You made me feel like everything’s alright yeah
You’re like the only butterfly in a hopeless world
거지 같은 세상 속 유일한 Butterfly
When I walk in the walk in the
walk in the street
Want you to stay it makes me excited yeah
너를 잡고 싶어서 난 안달났지 yeah
It’s dangerous outside the blanket
이불 밖은 위험해
Stay a little longer
좀 더 있길 원해
Drink some more
잔을 더 비워
Stay up all night with a single flame
불 하나로 지새는 이 밤
It’s just beginning
이제야 시작이잖아
Don’t make me fret
날 안달나게 하지 마
Whoa oh
What you waiting for
Oh Baby tell me
We got no time
Show me your move
Hope on to my rhythm like vroom
나의 리듬에 올라타 vroom
We bump and sounds like boom
우린 부딪혀 sounds like boom
Dream that I never wanna wake up
절대 깨고 싶지 않은 꿈
Let’s take it higher to the roof
Let’s take it 저 높이 to the roof
Count to 4 5 6 dance til that
Count to 4 5 6 까지 춤
Getting intense and it sounds like boom
좀 더 격해져 sounds like boom
It’s like an unforgettable dream
절대 지워지지 않을 꿈
Let’s take it higher to the moon
Let’s take it 더 높이 to the moon
Whoo
Unlike your cute face, your attitude is not
So cute한 외모와는 달리
So you’re stunning
그렇지 못한 태도 너는 빛이나
Got me on fire, can you feel me now?
내 맘에 불이 붙어 Feel me now?
Maybe I want you My sexy My sexy
널 갖고 싶나 봐 My sexy My sexy
You’re a masterpiece My classy My classic
한편의 명작 My classy My classic
Wanna make one a two I’m Fancy I’m Fancy
하나둘이 되고파 난 Fancy 난 Fancy
Shh let’s make a secret between the two of us oh
Shh 둘만의 비밀을 만들어가자 oh
Even though there’s no secrets forever
영원한 비밀은 없다 하더라도
Stay up all night with a single flame
불 하나로 지새는 이 밤
It’s just beginning
이제야 시작이잖아
Don’t make me fret
날 안달나게 하지 마
Whoa oh
What you waiting for
Oh Baby tell me
We got no time
Show me your move
Hope on to my rhythm like vroom
나의 리듬에 올라타 vroom
We bump and sounds like boom
우린 부딪혀 sounds like boom
Dream that I never wanna wake up
절대 깨고 싶지 않은 꿈
Let’s take it higher to the roof
Let’s take it 저 높이 to the roof
Count to 4 5 6 dance til that
Count to 4 5 6 까지 춤
Getting intense and it sounds like boom
좀 더 격해져 sounds like boom
It’s like an unforgettable dream
절대 지워지지 않을 꿈
Let’s take it higher to the moon
Let’s take it 더 높이 to the moon
It’s alright
Feeling wide awake baby
오감에 눈을 떠 Baby
Feel me
Crossing the line
선을 넘어와
Go beyond the limit
한계를 두지 마
We keep going yeah
우린 계속돼 yeah
Show me your move
Hope on to my rhythm like vroom
나의 리듬에 올라타 vroom
We bump and sounds like boom
우린 부딪혀 sounds like boom
Dream that I never wanna wake up
절대 깨고 싶지 않은 꿈
Let’s take it higher to the roof
Let’s take it 저 높이 to the roof
Count to 4 5 6 dance til that
Count to 4 5 6 까지 춤
Getting intense and it sounds like boom
좀 더 격해져 sounds like boom
It’s like an unforgettable dream
절대 지워지지 않을 꿈
Let’s take it higher to the moon
Let’s take it 더 높이 to the moon